eclincher.com 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy | eClincher

We at eClincher, Inc. (“Company”, ”we”, ”us”, ”our”) know that our users (“you”, ”your”) care about how their personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. Any capitalized terms used herein without definition shall have the meaning given to them in the Company Terms of Use.

1\.  What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use). If you are under 18, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 18 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at support@eclincher.com or our live chat.

2\.  What Information does the Company collect and how is it used?

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Services, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (described in this Section and in Section III below). We collect the following types of information:

 A.  Information you provide to us or give us permission to access and use on your behalf

We receive and store information you knowingly provide to us. We collect Personal Information such as your email address, first and last name, company name, phone number, billing information, questions or comments about our services, browser information, third-party encrypted account credentials, and generated content by you (such as messages, posts, comments, pages, profiles, images, feeds, or communications exchanged on the Supported Platforms).

If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, you understand, some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to sign up with us or to take advantage of some of our features. We may anonymize your Personal Information so that you cannot be individually identified, and provide that information to our partners.

How do we use your Personal Information or data:

– to identify you when you login to your account

– to contact you about your account and provide customer support, including responding to your questions and comments

– to enable us to operate the Services and provide them to you

– to keep you informed about our Services, features, surveys, blogs, offers, and events we think you may find useful

– to verify your transactions and for purchase confirmation, billing, security, and authentication

– to keep the Services safe and secure

– to analyze the Website or Services and information about our visitors and users, including research into our user demographics and user behaviour in order to improve our content and Services

– to share aggregate (non-identifiable) statistics about customers and users of our Services to prospective partners

–  to better understand your needs and the needs of users in the aggregate, diagnose problems, analyze trends, improve the features and usability of our Services, and better understand and market to our customers and users

We collect Personal Information from our customers and users in order to create account and subscribe to our Services (email, name, company name, phone number, billing information). With respect to this particular information, we’re the data controller.

We also process Personal Information on behalf of our customers and users as their data processor. For example, our customers and users use our Services to generate and publish Content (including, for example, information our customers create, monitor or collect from social media sites like Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc.). Our customers control how their Content is collected and used by them. In legal terms, this means that our customers and users are the data controller of their own generated Content. Accordingly, we only use the Content to provide Services to our customers and users in accordance with the lawful instructions they give us through our Services.

B.  Information Collected Automatically:

Whenever you interact with our Services, we automatically receive and record information about your activity on our website and Services. The informations is collected from your browser including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our Services’ features. If you click on an external link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to your browser. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.  
When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Website), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Services, so that we can make the Services appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

C. E-mail and Other Communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may send you promotional offers on behalf of other businesses, or communicate with you about your use of the Services. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make emails more interesting and improve our service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by selecting the opt-out option in emails received from the Company or by adjusting your account settings. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

3\.  Will the Company Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives?

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties as described below.

A.  Affiliated Businesses and Third Party Websites We Do Not Control: In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we are affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Services (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. One such service may include the ability for you to automatically transmit Third Party Account Information to your Website profile or to automatically transmit information in your Website profile to your third party account. We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such business or websites policies.

B.  Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

C.  Business Transfers: We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

D.  Protection of Company and Others: We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

E.  With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties in personally identifiable form, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

4\.  Is Personal Information about me secure?

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a third party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site’s privacy policy.

5\.  What personal information can I access?

Through your account settings, you may access and edit your password and email address. The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Services change. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at support@eclincher.com or via our live chat. You can also access all your generated Content, as part of using our Services. Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: support@eclincher.com or to our live chat support.

6\.  What Choices Do I Have and can I request my data?

You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features.  
You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in Section V above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request cancellation of any Premium Services by contacting us at support@eclincher.com or our live chat. Please note that some information may remain in our records after such cancellation. Additionally, if you cancel any Premium Services, the information associated with such Premium Services may not be recoverable if you reactivate such Premium Services. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

– User can delete personal data associated with his or her connected third party accounts (such as social media accounts). Open the Add & Manage Accounts popup and delete your accounts. User can also request all of his or her data to be deleted by requesting our Customer Support to delete his or her account (via live chat at our website).

– At any time, User can request his or her data by contacting our Customer Support via live chat on our website. After verifying the User identity, we will then export and email the data to the User. Available data for export: Inbox items and Auto Post Queues and posts.

– If User decide to leave our Services, or simply not using our Services, after 6 months of inactivity without log in to our app or platform, his or her data will be permanently deleted.

7\.  Cookie Policy

Cookies are small text files which a website may put on your computer or mobile device when you first visit a site or page. The cookie will help our Services, or another website, to recognize your device the next time you visit. For example, cookies can help us to remember your username and preferences, analyze how well our website is performing, or even allow us to recommend content we believe will be most relevant to you.

We may use cookies for the following reasons and purposes:

A.  To provide the service you have asked for. Some cookies are essential so you can navigate through the website and use its features. Without these cookies, we would not be able to provide the services you’ve requested. For example, some cookies allow us to identify subscribers and ensure they can access the subscription only pages. If a subscriber opts to disable these cookies, the user will not be able to access all of the content that a subscription entitles them to. These cookies don’t gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you’ve been on the internet. Essential cookies keep you logged in during your visit.

B.  To improve your browsing experience. These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make, such as your language or region and they provide improved features. These cookies will help remembering your preferences and settings, including marketing preferences, remembering if you’ve filled in certain forms, so you’re not asked to do it again, remembering if you’ve been to the Services before and restricting the number of times you’re shown a particular content or a promotion. We might also use these cookies to highlight Services that we think will be of interest to you based on your usage of the website.

C.  Analytics. To improve your experience on our Services, we like to keep track of what pages and links are popular and which ones don’t get used so much to help us keep our Services relevant and up to date. It’s also very useful to be able to identify trends of how people navigate (find their way through) our Services and if they get error messages from web pages. This group of cookies, often called “analytics cookies” are used to gather this information. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies you. The information collected is anonymous and is grouped with the information from everyone else’s cookies. We can then see the overall patterns of usage rather than any one person’s activity.

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. To do this, look at the “help” menu on your browser. Switching off cookies may restrict your use of the Services and/or delay or affect the way in which it operates.

8\.  International Transfer

Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including personal information, to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of information represents your agreement to that transfer.

9\.  Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted.

10\.  Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to support@eclincher.com, and we will try to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: May 1, 2018.
